Guide to the Harvey Williams Cushing Papers in the Yale University Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers held in Manuscripts and Archives, Part I
  - Correspondence, 1884-1939; Series I; 29 linear feet (70 boxes, 55 reels)
    - Bottomley, John T.
      See: Folders 1332-1334
    - Boudreau, Eugene N., 1924-1937 (Box 11, Folder 204, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folders 337-338
    - Bourguet, J., 1920-1930 (Box 11, Folder 205, Reel 9)
    - Bovie, W. T.
      See: Series II, Folders 229-231
    - Bowditch, Harold
      See: Series II, Folder 507
    - Bowen, Eugene B., 1921-1938 (Box 11, Folder 206, Reel 9)
    - Bowen, J. Nan Hoge
      See: Series II, Folder 882
    - Bowen, Julia, 1916-1939 (Box 11, Folder 207, Reel 9)
    - Bowers, Walter P., 1923-1932 (Box 11, Folder 208, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folders 245, 396, 632-635, 639, 641, 649, 652
    - Bowlby, Sir A.
      See: Series II, Folder 626
    - Bowler, John P., 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 209, Reel 9)
    - Boyd, Douglas, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 210, Reel 9)
    - Boyd, Walter W., 1930-1939 (Box 11, Folder 211, Reel 9)
    - Boyd, William, 1924-1935 (Box 11, Folder 212, Reel 9)
    - Boyden, Edward A., 1925-1936 (Box 11, Folder 213, Reel 9)
    - Bradford, Edward H., 1897-1924, undated (Box 11, Folder 214, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folders 365, 366
    - Bramwell, Edwin, 1906, 1921-1935 (Box 11, Folder 215, Reel 9)
    - Brasch, Frederick E., 1932-1934 (Box 11, Folder 216, Reel 9)
    - Bremer, Frédéric, 1921-1939 (Box 11, Folder 217, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folder 820
    - Brewer, George E., 1914-1936 (Box 11, Folder 218, Reel 9)
    - Brewster, Robert
      See: Series II, Folder 508
    - Brick Row Book Shop
      See: Series II, Folder 47
    - Brinkley, Mary H., 1914-1916, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 219, Reel 9)
    - British Base Hospital #22
      See: Series II, Folder 178
    - Brockbank, E. M., 1923-1935 (Box 11, Folder 220, Reel 9)
    - Brödel, Max, 1898-1934, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 221, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folder 745
    - Bromfield, Louis
      See: Series II, Folder 867
    - Brookline (Mass.), 1915-1934, undated (Box 11, Folder 222, Reel 9)
    - Brookline Country Club, 1917-1933 (Box 11, Folder 223, Reel 9)
    - Brookline Friendly Society, 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 224, Reel 9)
    - Brookline Public Library, 1925-1937 (Box 12, Folder 225, Reel 9)
    - Brooks, Barney, 1927-1935 (Box 12, Folder 226, Reel 9)
    - Broster, L. R., 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 227, Reel 9)
    - Brouwer, B., 1923-1938 (Box 12, Folder 228, Reel 9)
    - Brown, Alfred J., 1925-1933 (Box 12, Folder 229, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folders 897, 908
    - Brown, George P.
    - Brown, Horace Manchester, 1919-1927 (Box 12, Folder 230, Reel 9)
    - Brown, Huntington
      See: Series II, Folder 176
    - Brown, Lawrason, 1923-1936 (Box 12, Folder 231, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folder 508
    - Brown, Percy, 1930-1936, undated (Box 12, Folder 232, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folder 24
    - Brown, Preston
      See: Series II, Folder 15
    - Brown, Shipley and Co., 1920-1927, 1931-1934 (Box 12, Folder 233, Reel 9)
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman and Co., 1931-1939 (Box 12, Folder 234, Reel 9)
    - Buckley, R. C.
      See: Series II, Folder 747
    - Bucy, Paul C., 1932-1939 (Box 12, Folder 235, Reel 9)
    - Bühler, Curt F., 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 236, Reel 9)
    - Bump, Warren S.
      See: Series II, Folder 754
    - Burch, George
    - Burke, John
    - Burket, Walter C., 1915-1920 (Box 12, Folder 237, Reel 9)
    - Burlingham, L. H.
      See: Series II, Folders 794-795
    - Burrel, Virginia
      See: Series II, Folders 908-910
    - Busch, Edward, 1933-1939 (Box 12, Folder 238, Reel 9)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1919-1923 (Box 12, Folder 239, Reel 9)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 240, Reel 9)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1925-1927 (Box 12, Folder 241, Reel 9)
      See also: Series II, Folder 717
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1928-1931 (Box 12, Folder 242, Reel 10)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 243, Reel 10)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 244, Reel 10)
    - Bushnell, Edward, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 245, Reel 10)
    - Byers, Gordon H.
    - Byrnes, Charles M., 1915-1921, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 246, Reel 10)
    - Cab-Cam (Box 12, Folder 247, Reel 10)
    - Can-Cap (Box 13, Folder 248, Reel 10)
    - Car (Box 13, Folder 249, Reel 10)
    - Cas-Caw (Box 13, Folder 250, Reel 10)
    - Ce-Che (Box 13, Folder 251, Reel 10)
    - Chi-Cho (Box 13, Folder 252, Reel 10)
    - Chr-Cla (Box 13, Folder 253, Reel 10)
    - Cle-Coh (Box 13, Folder 254, Reel 10)
    - Col (Box 13, Folder 255, Reel 10)
    - Com-Con (Box 13, Folder 256, Reel 10)
    - Coo-Cot (Box 13, Folder 257, Reel 10)
    - Cou-Cr (Box 13, Folder 258, Reel 11)
    - Cu-Cy (Box 13, Folder 259, Reel 11)
    - Cabot, Richard C., 1899, 1904, 1921-1938 (Box 14, Folder 260, Reel 11)
    - Cairns, Hugh William Bell, 1925-1929 (Box 14, Folder 261, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folder 664
    - Cairns, Hugh William Bell, 1930-1935 (Box 14, Folder 262, Reel 11)
    - Cairns, High William Bell, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 263, Reel 11)
    - Camac, Charles N. B., 1897-1907, 1917-1933 (Box 14, Folder 264, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folder 516
    - Cameron, Irving
      See: Series II, Folder 514
    - Campbell, Charles Macfie, 1920-1938 (Box 14, Folder 265, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folder 653
    - Campbell, Edith C.
      See: Series II, Folder 640
    - Campbell, Eldridge H., 1935-1939 (Box 14, Folder 266, Reel 11)
    - Cannon, Walter B., 1906-1927 (Box 14, Folder 267, Reel 11)
      See also: Folders 28-29, 1026; Series II, Folders 6, 333-335, 864
    - Cannon, Walter B., 1928-1933 (Box 14, Folder 268, Reel 11)
      See also: Folders 30, 1026; Series II, Folders 333-335
    - Cannon, Walter B., 1934-1939 (Box 14, Folder 269, Reel 11)
    - Carnegie Institution, 1920, 1931, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 270, Reel 11)
    - Carpenter, E. R., 1924-1931 (Box 14, Folder 271, Reel 11)
    - Carrel, Alexis, 1905-1913, 1917-1939 (Box 14, Folder 272, Reel 11)
    - Castiglioni, Arturo, 1933-1939 (Box 14, Folder 273, Reel 11)
    - Cattell, Henry W.
    - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1915-1937 (Box 14, Folder 274, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folders 637, 639
    - Census of Fifteenth Century Books Owned in America (2nd), 1936-1938 (Box 14, Folder 275, Reel 11)
    - Century Association; Century Club, 1916-1939 (Box 14, Folder 276, Reel 11)
    - Cerrato, Calvin M., 1932-1938 (Box 14, Folder 277, Reel 11)
    - Chamberlain, F. B.
      See: Series II, Folder 717
    - Chance, Burton, 1920-1936 (Box 14, Folder 278, Reel 11)
    - Chapin, Adèle, 1890, 1933-1935, undated (Box 14, Folder 279, Reel 11)
    - Chapin, Susan, 1917-1939, undated (Box 14, Folder 280, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folder 514
    - Chapin, William A. R.
    - Charaka Club, 1914-1938 (Box 14, Folder 281, Reel 11)
    - Chase, Franklin H.
      See: Series II, Folder 837
    - Chatard, J. A.
    - Cheatle, Sir George Lenthal, 1921-1923 (Box 14, Folder 282, Reel 11)
    - Cheever, David, 1912, 1915, 1926-1936 (Box 14, Folder 283, Reel 11)
      See also: Series II, Folders 780, 782-789
    - Chesney, Alan
      See: Series II, Folders 647, 655
    - Chez Durtal
      See: Series II, Folder 55
    - Chicago Surgical Society
      See: Series II, Folder 35
    - Chidester, D. D.
    - Chidester, F. E., 1932-1936 (Box 14, Folder 284, Reel 11)
    - Childs, Starling W., 1914-1929 (Box 15, Folder 285, Reel 12)
    - Childs, Starling W., 1930-1939 (Box 15, Folder 286, Reel 12)
    - Childs (S.W.) Management Corporation, 1922-1930 (Box 15, Folder 287, Reel 12)
    - Christian, Henry A., 1926-1938 (Box 15, Folder 288, Reel 12)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386-388, 396, 771, 778-791
    - Christiansen, Viggo, 1922-1933 (Box 15, Folder 289, Reel 12)
    - Christopher, Frederic
    - Churchill, Edward D., 1919-1939 (Box 15, Folder 290, Reel 12)
      See also: Series II, Folders 364, 434-437
    - Churchman, John W., 1916-1928 (Box 15, Folder 291, Reel 12)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386-387, 514
    - Citizens Savings and Trust Co., 1920 (Box 15, Folder 292, Reel 12)
    - Clark, Burton Jr.
      See: Series II, Folder 340
    - Clark, Charles U., 1921-1938 (Box 15, Folder 293, Reel 12)
    - Clark, Harold T., 1928-1936 (Box 15, Folder 294, Reel 12)
    - Clarke, Henry Martyn
      See: Series II, Folder 911
    - Clemons, Elizabeth White
      See: Series II, Folder 624
    - Clendening, Logan, 1932-1939 (Box 15, Folder 295, Reel 12)
    - Cleveland Medical Library Association, 1926-1938 (Box 15, Folder 296, Reel 12)
    - Clifford, Carl E.
      See: Series II, Folder 25
    - Club of Odd Volumes, 1911-1933 (Box 15, Folder 297, Reel 12)
    - Cobb, Stanley, 1915-1937 (Box 15, Folder 298, Reel 12)
    - Cochrane, Alexander
      See: Series II, Folder 778-780
    - Cock, F. William, 1923-1934 (Box 15, Folder 299, Reel 12)
    - Codding, Mildred
      See: Series II, Folder 664
    - Codman, Edmund D.
      See: Series II, Folder 809
    - Codman, Ernest Amory, 1894-1911, 1920-1937, undated (Box 15, Folder 300, Reel 12)
    - Cohen, Benjamin
    - Cohen, Max
    - Cohn, Alfred E., 1928-1939 (Box 15, Folder 301, Reel 12)
    - Cole, Rufus, 1909-1932 (Box 15, Folder 302, Reel 12)
      See also: Series II, Folder 714
    - Coley, William B., 1914-1934 (Box 15, Folder 303, Reel 12)
    - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1907, 1928-1936, undated (Box 15, Folder 304, Reel 12)
      See also: Folder 1141
    - Coller, Frederick A., 1931-1937 (Box 15, Folder 305, Reel 12)
    - Committee on Economic Security
      See: Series II, Folders 193-213
    - Committee on Graduate Studies in France, 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 306, Reel 12)
    - Community Health Association, 1925-1929 (Box 15, Folder 307, Reel 12)
    - Comrie, John D., 1924-1936 (Box 15, Folder 308, Reel 12)
    - Conant, James B.
      See: Series II, Folder 174
    - Congress of American Physicians and Surgeons, 1922-1928, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 309, Reel 12)
    - Congress of American Physicians and Surgeons, 1934-1938 (Box 15, Folder 310, Reel 12)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1915-1936 (Box 15, Folder 311, Reel 12)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1925-1939 (Box 15, Folder 312, Reel 12)
    - Connor, Charles L., 1926-1939 (Box 15, Folder 313, Reel 12)
    - Cooley, Charles P., 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 314, Reel 13)
    - Coolidge, Charles
      See: Series II, Folders 15-18
    - Coolidge and Shattuck, Architects
      See: Series II, Folder 14
    - Coombs, Herbert I., 1928-1936 (Box 16, Folder 315, Reel 13)
    - Copeland, Charles T., 1916-1938 (Box 16, Folder 316, Reel 13)
    - Corner, George W., 1926-1939 (Box 16, Folder 317, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folders 395, 866
    - Cornil, Lucien, 1921-1936 (Box 16, Folder 318, Reel 13)
    - Corning, H. K., 1920-1927 (Box 16, Folder 319, Reel 13)
    - Costigan, Mary L.
    - Cottam, Geoffery I. W.
      See: Series II, Folder 744
    - Councilman, Elizabeth, 1933-1936 (Box 16, Folder 320, Reel 13)
    - Councilman, W. T., 1909-1918 (Box 16, Folder 321, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folders 215b, 732-743
    - Councilman, W. T. Councilman, Isa, 1919-1933 (Box 16, Folder 322, Reel 13)
    - Courtney, Joseph W., 1922-1927 (Box 16, Folder 323, Reel 13)
    - Courville, Cyril B., 1928-1939 (Box 16, Folder 324, Reel 13)
    - Cowdry, E. V., 1921-1934 (Box 16, Folder 325, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folder 220
    - Coy, George
      See: Series II, Folder 515
    - Craig, Winchell McKendree, 1929-1938 (Box 16, Folder 326, Reel 13)
    - Crawford, Albert S., 1925-1939 (Box 16, Folder 327, Reel 13)
    - Crawford, Frank, 1917-1938 (Box 16, Folder 328, Reel 13)
    - Crighton, Annie
      See: Series II, Folder 494
    - Crile, George W., 1914-1938, undated (Box 16, Folder 329, Reel 13)
      See also: Folder 40; Series II, Folders 1-4, 12, 172
    - Crosby, Raymond M., 1929-1937 (Box 16, Folder 330, Reel 13)
    - Croskey, John Welsh
    - Cross, Wilbur L., 1915-1938 (Box 16, Folder 331, Reel 13)
      See also: Folder 1574
    - Crothers, Bronson, 1923-1939 (Box 16, Folder 332, Reel 13)
    - Crouch, J. E.
    - Crowe, Samuel J., 1911-1939 (Box 16, Folder 333, Reel 13)
    - Crowell, Benedict, 1919-1925 (Box 16, Folder 334, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folder 22
    - Crowley, Jerome W.
      See: Series II, Folder 227
    - Cruikshank, F. S.
      See: Series II, Folders 391, 393
    - Crummer, Leroy, 1922-1938 (Box 16, Folder 335, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folders 189, 390, 907-908
    - Crummer, Myrtle, 1923-1939 (Box 16, Folder 336, Reel 13)
    - Crump, G. Curtis, 1927-1931 (Box 16, Folder 337, Reel 13)
      See also: Series II, Folders 654, 747
    - Cullen, G. Matheson
      See: Series II, Folder 909
    - Cullen, Thomas S.
    - Cummin, John W., 1922-1939 (Box 16, Folder 338, Reel 13)
    - Cummins, S. Lyle, 1920-1926, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 339, Reel 13)
    - Cunard Steamship Company, 1922-1927 (Box 17, Folder 340, Reel 13)
    - Curtis, Charles P.
      See: Series II, Folders 9, 780-791, 809
    - Cushing, Arthur A., 1924-1937 (Box 17, Folder 341, Reel 13)
    - Cushing, Arthur R.
      See: Series II, Folder 188
    - Cushing, Barbara, 1920-1939, undated (Box 17, Folder 342, Reel 13)
    - Cushing, Betsey
      See: Folder 1223
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1884-1888 May (Box 17, Folder 343, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1888 June- 1889 (Box 17, Folder 344, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 345, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1891 (Box 17, Folder 346, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1892 (Box 17, Folder 347, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1893 (Box 17, Folder 348, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1894-1897 (Box 17, Folder 349, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams: trip to Bermuda, 1896 February (Box 17, Folder 350, Reel 14)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1898-1900 (Box 17, Folder 351, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Betsey Maria Williams, 1901-1903 (Box 17, Folder 352, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Carolyn, 1892, 1913, 1920-1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 353, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Edward Fitch, 1891-1910, undated (Box 17, Folder 354, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Edward Harvey, 1915-1933 (Box 18, Folder 355, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Edward Harvey, 1934-1939 (Box 18, Folder 356, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Florence, 1921-1936, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 357, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, George B., 1914-1939 (Box 18, Folder 358, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, H. P., 1914-1921 (Box 18, Folder 359, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Haywood W., 1898-1934 (Box 18, Folder 360, Reel 15)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1887-1888 May (Box 18, Folder 361, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1888 June-1889 (Box 18, Folder 362, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 363, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1891-1892 (Box 18, Folder 364, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 365, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1894-1897 (Box 18, Folder 366, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1898-1900 (Box 18, Folder 367, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1901-1902 (Box 19, Folder 368, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 369, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1904-1906 (Box 19, Folder 370, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, 1907-1910 (Box 19, Folder 371, Reel 16)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, Jr., 1918-1928 (Box 19, Folder 372, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, Jr., 1929-1939 (Box 19, Folder 373, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Henry Kirke, Jr.: insurance, 1932-1939 (Box 19, Folder 374, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1891-1894 (Box 19, Folder 375, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1895-1898 March (Box 19, Folder 376, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1898 April- August (Box 20, Folder 377, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1898 September-December (Box 20, Folder 378, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1899 (Box 20, Folder 379, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 380, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 381, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1902 (Box 20, Folder 382, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1903-1904 (Box 20, Folder 383, Reel 17)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1905-1907 (Box 21, Folder 384, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1908-1909 (Box 21, Folder 385, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 386, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 387, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1915-1916 (Box 21, Folder 388, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 389, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1918 January-May (Box 21, Folder 390, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1918 June-December (Box 21, Folder 391, Reel 18)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1919-1923 (Box 21, Folder 392, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1924-1925, 1929, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 393, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, Katherine Stone Crowell, 1932-1939, undated (Box 21, Folder 394, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, Kirke W., 1914-1915 (Box 21, Folder 395, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, Mary B., 1911-1938, undated (Box 21, Folder 396, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, Mélanie Harvey, 1911-1939, undated (Box 21, Folder 397, Reel 19)
      See also: Folder 663
    - Cushing, William E., 1877, 1892, 1910-1917, undated (Box 22, Folder 398, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, William H., 1912-1920 June (Box 22, Folder 399, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, William H., 1920 July-1921 (Box 22, Folder 400, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, William H., 1922-1923 (Box 22, Folder 401, Reel 19)
    - Cushing, William H., 1924-1927, undated (Box 22, Folder 402, Reel 19)
    - Cushny, Arthur R.
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1914-1925 (Box 22, Folder 403, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 440-444, 782-783, 846
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1926-1928 (Box 22, Folder 404, Reel 19)
      See also: Folder 39; Series II, Folders 192, 403, 430-433, 440-444, 446, 791; MHL
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 405, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 364, 430-433, 440-444, 446, 791; MHL
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1931-1935 (Box 22, Folder 406, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-175, 403, 408, 430-433, 437, 446, 458-459, 791
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 407, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-175, 458-459
    - Cutler, Elliott C., 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 408, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-175
    - Cutter, Irving S., 1928-1939 (Box 22, Folder 409, Reel 19)
      See also: Series II, Folders 395-396
    - Da (Box 22, Folder 410, Reel 19)
    - De (Box 22, Folder 411, Reel 20)
    - Di (Box 23, Folder 412, Reel 20)
    - Do (Box 23, Folder 413, Reel 20)
    - Dr (Box 23, Folder 414, Reel 20)
    - Du (Box 23, Folder 415, Reel 20)
    - Da Costa, John Chalmers, 1906-1907, 1919-1931 (Box 23, Folder 416, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folders 36, 520
    - Dana, Charles L., 1901-1908, 1914-1927 (Box 23, Folder 417, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386, 709
    - Dandy, Walter E., 1919-1934 (Box 23, Folder 418, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folder 665
    - Darey, Herbert J.
      See: Series II, Folder 520
    - Darrach, William, 1919-1931 (Box 23, Folder 419, Reel 20)
    - Dartmouth College, 1928-1929 (Box 23, Folder 420, Reel 20)
    - Davidoff, Leo M., 1926-1938 (Box 23, Folder 421, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folders 665, 754, 765
    - Davies, J. Davies, Rose and Co.
      See: Series II, Folders 447-449
    - Davis, Hallowell, 1921-1932 (Box 23, Folder 422, Reel 20)
    - Davis, John Staige, 1915-1922 (Box 23, Folder 423, Reel 20)
    - Davis, Lincoln, 1914-1934 (Box 23, Folder 424, Reel 20)
    - Davis, Loyal E., 1923-1939 (Box 23, Folder 425, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-177, 641, 644, 754
    - Davis and Orioli
      See: Series II, Folders 53-54
    - Davison, H. P., 1921 (Box 23, Folder 426, Reel 20)
    - Davison, Wilburt C., 1925-1938 (Box 23, Folder 427, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folder 520
    - Dawson, James W., 1925-1929 (Box 23, Folder 428, Reel 20)
    - Day, George Parmly Day, Wilhelmine, 1916-1939 (Box 23, Folder 429, Reel 20)
      See also: Folder 1577; Series II, Folders 218, 235, 520, 906, 907
    - Day, Hilbert F., 1914-1936 (Box 23, Folder 430, Reel 20)
    - Dayton, Theodore R., 1925-1932 (Box 23, Folder 431, Reel 20)
    - Deane, Jane, 1926-1930 (Box 23, Folder 432, Reel 20)
    - Decker, Pierre, 1934-1937 (Box 23, Folder 433, Reel 20)
    - DeCoppet, Gaston
    - Deery, Edwin M., 1929-1938 (Box 23, Folder 434, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folder 821
    - de Grosz, Emile, 1928-1939 (Box 24, Folder 435, Reel 20)
    - Delevan, D. Bryson, 1916, 1937, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 436, Reel 20)
      See also: Series II, Folder 4
    - DeLint, J. G., 1922-1926 (Box 24, Folder 437, Reel 20)
    - Derby, George S., 1915-1932 (Box 24, Folder 438, Reel 20)
    - Derow, Harry E.
    - Desmond, J. J.
      See: Series II, Folder 718
    - Deutsche Akademie der Naturforschur, 1932-1934 (Box 24, Folder 439, Reel 21)
    - Dew, Harold R., 1930-1934 (Box 24, Folder 440, Reel 21)
    - Dexter, Richard
      See: Series II, Folder 641
    - Diller, Theodore, 1924-1927 (Box 24, Folder 441, Reel 21)
    - Dimond, Hugh J., 1923, 1927- 1932 (Box 24, Folder 442, Reel 21)
    - Doe, Janet, 1931-1939 (Box 24, Folder 443, Reel 21)
    - Donald, William M.
      See: Series II, Folder 521
    - Donaldson, Henry H., 1911-1936 (Box 24, Folder 444, Reel 21)
    - Donati, Mario, 1933-1937 (Box 24, Folder 445, Reel 21)
    - Donley, John E., Jr., 1914-1939 (Box 24, Folder 446, Reel 21)
    - Donnelly, Joseph L.
    - Donnelly, Thomas E., 1922-1938 (Box 24, Folder 447, Reel 21)
    - Dott, Norman M., 1924-1938 (Box 24, Folder 448, Reel 21)
      See also: Series II, Folder 755
    - Dover, Violette M.
    - Dowling, Ernesto, 1926-1929, undated (Box 24, Folder 449, Reel 21)
    - Dowling, John J.
      See: Series II, Folder 361
    - Dowman, Charles E., 1919-1928 (Box 24, Folder 450, Reel 21)
    - Drinker, Cecil K., 1926-1931 (Box 24, Folder 451, Reel 21)
    - Drury, Dana W., 1929-1932, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 452, Reel 21)
    - Drury, Samuel S., 1929-1938 (Box 24, Folder 453, Reel 21)
    - Duckett, J. W.
    - Duggan, Patrick, 1921-1929 (Box 24, Folder 454, Reel 21)
    - Dunn, John Shaw, 1923-1928 (Box 24, Folder 455, Reel 21)
    - Durrett, J. J.
      See: Series II, Folder 292
    - Dusser de Barenne, John, 1931-1938 (Box 24, Folder 456, Reel 21)
    - Ea-Ec (Box 25, Folder 457, Reel 21)
    - Ed-Ei (Box 25, Folder 458, Reel 21)
    - El (Box 25, Folder 459, Reel 21)
    - Em-Eu (Box 25, Folder 460, Reel 21)
    - Ev-Ey (Box 25, Folder 461, Reel 21)
    - Eagleton, Wells P., 1915-1932 (Box 25, Folder 462, Reel 21)
    - Eberts, Edmund M. von, 1916-1936 (Box 25, Folder 463, Reel 21)
      See also: Series II, Folder 523
    - Eckels, John C.
      See: Series II, Folder 341
    - Eckstein, Gustav, 1924-1937 (Box 25, Folder 464, Reel 21)
    - Edsall, David L., 1910-1915 (Box 25, Folder 465, Reel 21)
      See also: Folder 1216; Series II, Folders 20, 325-332, 361, 362, 364-378, 381-382, 434-435, 454, 457-459
    - Edwards, Clarence
    - Einstein, Albert, 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 466, Reel 21)
    - Eiselberg, Anton von, 1910, 1920- 1939 (Box 25, Folder 467, Reel 21)
    - Eiselberg, Otto, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 468, Reel 21)